[Music]
Life is uncertain and unpredictable. The
next step is to face a storm.
With the right term plan, you
can rest assured that whether the days are good
or bad, you and your Priya Jain are
financially secure for the future.
Introducing ICICI Priya
Protect Smart, a term plan that provides financial security for you and
your family up to 99 years of age
and
gives you the flexibility to choose the plan option that best suits
your needs. This plan
offers combined protection against life cover, terminal illness, critical illness, and permanent disability. Let's understand it in detail.
[Music] In case of
diagnosis of a terminal illness,
life cover is paid to Namita,
and in case of permanent disability due to an accident,
future premiums under the policy are
waived. The
second option is the Life Plus option.
In this option, along with the benefits under the Life option, the
life assured is
also covered for an accidental death benefit.
In case of death due to an accident during the Accidental Death Benefit Term,
Namita
receives an accidental death benefit in addition to the life cover. The
third option is the Life and Health option.
Under the Live Option,
along with the benefits, the life assured
also gets Accelerated Critical Illness Benefit. The
plan covers against 34 critical illnesses. On diagnosis of the covered critical illness, the life assured will receive
a lump sum payment to meet his/her financial needs. The
fourth and final
option is the All-in-One Option which
covers both death benefit and accelerated critical illness benefit.
This plan also offers the flexibility to pay the premium once, for a
limited period or during the entire policy
term.
What's more, this plan offers
tax benefits on premiums paid. ICC
PRIT Smart
allows you to take the Live Tax in a manner that
meets your financial needs. The Live Tax can be
paid to your beneficiary in the following options: First, a
lump sum benefit in which the entire benefit amount is paid in
one lump sum; Second, a lump sum benefit in
which 10% of the benefit amount is paid to the beneficiary
every year for 10 years; Third,
a lump sum benefit in which a percentage of the
sum assured is paid in lump sum
at the outset.  The choice is made and the
remaining amount is paid
in installments from the society for 10 years in advance. The
fourth and final option is the benefit of the scheme called the Badhni IAY, in
which the benefit is
paid in installments from the society for 10 years, starting
with a 10% annual benefit amount in the first year. The income amount increases at a simple rate at
10% per annum. Now let's
see how this plan works. Riya is a
32 year old working professional. She has taken a plan to
buy a house.
Understanding the need for security in her fast paced life, she has invested Rs.
18000 in ICICI PRI Protect Smart with Life Cover of Rs. 1 crore and Critical Illness Benefit of Rs. 25 lakh for 30 years.
Now at the age of 40, Riya is
diagnosed with a critical illness. At this
time, she will get Rs. 25 lakh
[Music] which will
reduce proportionately to Rs.
8959 per annum. Now
in case of Riya's unfortunate death, her son
Namita will get Rs. 75 lakh.  A maximum death benefit will be
received and the policy will terminate
Secure your future today with ICICI Prudential Income Protect Smart Plan
[Music]
[Applause]